https://www.advancedlabeling.com/privacy

Advanced Labeling & Marking > Home
Login
Search
Products
Inkjet SystemsLinx - Small CharacterLeibinger - Small CharacterFoxjet - High ResHigh Res ControllersHigh Res PrintheadsFoxjet SoloSeriesFoxjet Vx Series - IncDigital Design - Evo - High ResDiagraph - Large Character (DOD) - IncDiagraph Large Character Inkjet Printers - IncDiagraph IJ 3000 - IncDiagraph Inks & MSDS - IncThermal PrintersSATO AmericaTharoDatamax-HoneywellZebraColor PrintersSwiftcolorAfiniaPrimera PrintersLabeling Systems - IncUniversal Labeling Systems - IncSemi-AutomaticAutomatic LabelersPrint and Apply MainApplicatorsCTM Labeling SystemsAuto Labe - IncSemi Automatic Labelers - IncLabel Appliers - IncPrint and Apply - IncPrimera Labelers - IncStart International - XAutomatic Tape Dispensers - XCarouselHeavy DutyIndustrial Tape DispensersLight DutyProgrammableSafety Guard SystemGummed Tape DispensersHandheld Label ApplicatorsIndustrial Label DispensersManual Label DispensersManual Tape DispensersBag SealersDefinite LengthHand Held Tape GunsLiner RemoversMulti-PurposeStandardSpecialty - Bottle Labelers, Rewinders and Die-CutsLabeling SoftwareSeagull ScientificTeklynxTharoProductivityFactracRibbons and LabelsCustom LabelsStock Labels MainThermal Transfer Ribbon Main
Service
Contact Us
Label Quote
About Us
News & Events
Products
Service
Contact Us
Advanced Labeling & Marking is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology
that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy
applies to the Advanced Labeling & Marking Web site and governs data collection and usage.
By using the Advanced Labeling & Marking website, you consent to the data practices described
in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Advanced Labeling & Marking collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail
address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Advanced Labeling & Marking also
collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as
your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically
collected by Advanced Labeling & Marking. This information can include: your IP address,
browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This
information is used by Advanced Labeling & Marking for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use
of the Advanced Labeling & Marking Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information
or personally sensitive data through Advanced Labeling & Marking public message boards,
this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Advanced Labeling & Marking
does not read any of your private online communications.
Advanced Labeling & Marking encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites
you choose to link to from Advanced Labeling & Marking so that you can understand how those
Web sites collect, use and share your information. Advanced Labeling & Marking is not responsible
for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Advanced Labeling & Marking
and Advanced Labeling & Marking family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Advanced Labeling & Marking collects and uses your personal information to operate the Advanced Labeling & Marking
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Advanced Labeling & Marking also uses
your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services
available from Advanced Labeling & Marking and its affiliates. Advanced Labeling & Marking may also
contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services
or of potential new services that may be offered.
Advanced Labeling & Marking does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Advanced Labeling & Marking may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business
partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases,
your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone
number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Advanced Labeling & Marking
may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send
you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All
such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to
provide these services to Advanced Labeling & Marking, and they are required to maintain
the confidentiality of your information.
Advanced Labeling & Marking does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such
as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Advanced Labeling & Marking keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within
Advanced Labeling & Marking, in order to determine what Advanced Labeling & Marking services are
the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising
within Advanced Labeling & Marking to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested
in a particular subject area.
Advanced Labeling & Marking Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice,
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is
necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process
served on Advanced Labeling & Marking or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or
property of Advanced Labeling & Marking; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect
the personal safety of users of Advanced Labeling & Marking, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Advanced Labeling & Marking Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online
experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page
server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.
Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the
domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save
you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned
to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Advanced Labeling & Marking pages, or
register with Advanced Labeling & Marking site or services, a cookie helps Advanced Labeling & Marking
to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process
of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses,
and so on. When you return to the same Advanced Labeling & Marking Web site, the information
you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Advanced Labeling & Marking
features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically
accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies
if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the Advanced Labeling & Marking services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Advanced Labeling & Marking secures your personal information from unauthorized access,
use or disclosure. Advanced Labeling & Marking secures the personally identifiable information
you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from
unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit
card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use
of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Advanced Labeling & Marking will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect
company and customer feedback. Advanced Labeling & Marking encourages you to periodically
review this Statement to be informed of how Advanced Labeling & Marking is protecting your
information.
Contact Information
Advanced Labeling & Marking welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.
If you believe that Advanced Labeling & Marking has not adhered to this Statement, please
contact Advanced Labeling & Marking at jasond@advancedlabeling.com.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the
problem.
Copyright 2020 by Advanced Labeling & Marking
|  Terms Of Use  |  Privacy Statement
